(尼泊尔 辛杜帕尔乔克地区)
起来
Up!
还是不肯说吗
Still doesn't not want to talk?
好吧
Very well!
你会死得很难看
You will die a brutal death.
(坏脾气)
(马上就来)
你给我开稳一点 托尔
Keep this sucka steady, Toll!
我尽力了
I'll do my best.
开始吧
Here we go!
来吧 混蛋
Come on, you bastards!
去死
Eat shit!
你最好蹲下
You better duck!
噢 见鬼
Oh, shit!
怎么回事
快关门
掩护
Turn around...
(敲敲门)
分头行动
Break!
小心碰头 混蛋
Watch your handling, slick!
闭嘴 贡纳
Shut up, Gunner.
爽到家了
Gunnar love it!
有直升机
Incoming chopper!
得把那玩意儿打下来
We gotta get this thing outta here!
打下来 你有主意吗
You got any ideas?
我在问你呢
That's what I'm asking you.
我还想问你呢
Well I'm asking you!
安全
Clear!
我去
I got this.
不肯说是吧 那就去死吧
Think you're tough? Did your team arrive?
托尔 扶他起来
Toll Road, get 'em up.
战壕
Trench?
噢 真是太丢人了
Oh, this is embarrassing.
丢到家了
Yeah, sure is.
他来这儿干嘛
What's he doing here?
我来营救那个中国富豪
Saving this Chinese billionaire.
噢 是吗 有意思 我们也是
Oh yeah? That's funny. So are we.
看来我们接了同一个任务 对吗
Looks like we're in a sketchy problem, aren't we?
快帮我解开 科学怪人
Cut me loose! Frankenstein.
别生气 贡纳
Don't get nuts, Gunner.
解开吧
Do it.
- 你的团队呢 - 在等我
- Where's your team? - Waiting.
我需要武器 大家伙 这个不错
I need a weapon, something big. Yours!
我的大家伙不会借给别人的
My big weapon's hangin' right where it is.
行了 你还有把备用的
Come on, Caesar, you got a back-up.
你敢借了不还 我就终结了你
If I don't get this back, your ass is terminated.
你想得美
In your dreams.
你跟我们一起走吧
Trench, We've got a way out.
谢谢 我自有办法
Thanks, I got my own.
我们带你出去 伙计
Let's get you out of here, pal.
听着 我不想打扰你们两个
Hey look, I hate to break up the bromance.
可我们晚了20秒
We're 20 seconds late.
快带大款出去
Get money bags up!
连谢谢都不会说
A 'thank you' would be nice.
我不想欠人情
I hate owing you.
你已经欠了 伙计
What'll you do, big boy?
我们走 阴阳
Let's go, Yang!
你赢了
You in?
那还用问
Of course, I'm in.
快走
Let's go!
我也上去
I'm out.
现在才戴幸运戒指
Now you put on your lucky ring?
洗个澡吧
One wet wall coming up!
有本事都冲我来啊
I got the gangbang right here!
我掩护你
I've got your back!
继续前进
Keep moving!
- 见鬼 - 跳下去
- Oh shit! - Here we go!
- 怎么总是我 - 你中枪了
- Why always me? - Are you hit?
是啊 两枪
Yeah, twice..
你的运气好
Better you than me.
你真会安慰人
That's nice, nice.
把枪放下
你叫了客房服务
You order room service?
好像没有
Not really.
这个结局太蹩脚了
Then this could be a pissy ending.
放下枪 放下
这也能用
Not loaded?
但愿能管用
We could only hope.
对不起 长官 我在测算风速
Sorry sir, I had to adjust for a windshift.
没关系 去最后那个位置
No problem, hit the last position.
收到 完毕
Moving out, over.
快 快 快
Let's go.. go.. go!
快开 快啊
GO, go!
坚持住 我们来了
OK, hold on ladies. The cavalry's here.
你们怎么这么慢
About time you got here!
准备开火
Wake up Sam.
好的
On it.
见鬼
Shit!
那孩子真棒
This guy's good.
干得漂亮
You're good.
谢谢 长官
Appreciate it, sir.
我们会调头来接你
I swear I'll pick you up, Kid.
我会准时到
Won't be late, sir.
快
Go!
行了 伙计们 该回家了
Alright guys, put your toys away.
瞄准目标
Target in sight!
- 准备就绪 - 开火
- Souped up! - Fire!
你打偏了
You missed.
你瞄偏了
You're aiming!
开火
Fire!
这才像样
That was a statement.
快走吧
Hit it!
扔掉摩托艇
Dump the ski!
快 把它丢下去
Come on, we need to lose weight!
飞起来 宝贝
Climb, baby!
起来
Climb!
飞机没起来
It ain't getting up!
有幸运戒指
Lucky ring.
幸运戒指
《敢死队2》
(中国 河北省)
我们离北京大约还有20英里
We are approximately 20 miles out of Beijing.
虽然我不想问
Not that I want to hear it,
- 油压怎么样了 - 显示错误
- but what's the oil pressure? - Faulty.
好吧 那高度仪呢
Great! And the altimeter?
你相信吗 卡在10000英尺了
Can you believe it? Stuck at 10,000 ft.
- 液压器呢 - 什么液压器
- Hydraulics? - What hydraulics?
恭喜你 你又多了个垃圾
Congratulations, you flew another piece of junk.
等你有空 我们聊聊
Hey can we talk when you're not too busy?
没问题
Sure, anytime.
这孩子真棒
Kid's amazing.
是吗 我也很棒
Really? So am I.
只不过你习惯了
You're just used up.
让客户准备好
Get the client ready!
这是要干嘛
What is going on?
你要抄近路回家了 伙计
Looks like you're taking a shortcut home, pal.
降落伞好吗
Parachute good?
降落伞
Parachute?
为什么要背降落伞
Why are you gonna parachute?
他们居然把降落许可时间改到了明天
Do you believe they changed the landing party to tomorrow?
是啊 不过没关系 他可以早点回家
Yeah, it's OK, I'll get home a little earlier.
15秒准备
15 seconds.
舱门打开了
Opening the hatch!
阴阳 从大款安全到家
Yang, get money bags home safely.
你什么时候回来
So when are you coming back?
也许很快 也许不回来
Maybe soon, maybe never.
也许换个工作
Maybe try a new life.
你走了我戏弄谁啊
Then who am I supposed to pick on?
一定会有人顶我缺的
You will find another minority.
阴阳
Yang!
笑一个
Smile...
后会有期 大鳄鱼
See you later, alligator.
走吧
再见了 各位
正宗的中式外卖
Now that's a real Chinese takeout.
开快点 我想家了
Floor it, I'm homesick.
遵命
You got it.
(老了点酒吧)
我爱这首歌
I love this song!
圣诞 我的朋友
Christmas, my friend..
我说你不会真的要这么做吧
Please tell me you ain't going through with this.
当然了 瞧她多美 谁不想娶她
Course I am. Look at that girl, who wouldn't marry her.
她对你不忠
She cheated on you.
那叫 半不忠
It was a half-cheat.
怎么说
Which is...
就是半真半假 你又没证据 传言不靠谱
The other side of her, half-truth.
不靠谱 我不想泼你冷水
Murky. I hate to break this to you, pal.
可你要是娶了她 就能开帽子专卖店了
But your girlfriend over there has a world-class cheating gene.
我真该一刀捅死你
I should stab you in the heart.
太晚了
Too late.
嗨 干杯
Hi, cheers.
我以前觉得你的心是黑的
You know I used to think you had a black heart.
岂止是黑啊
Black is too colorful.
- 嗨 宝贝 - 嗨
- Hey babe! - Hey!
- 嗨 巴尼 - 嗨 莱西
- Hey Barney! - Hey Lacy.
答应我 下次别把我的宝贝带走这么久
Promise next time not to keep my baby away so long?
我用良心保证
Cross my heart.
他没良心
If he had one.
看谁在神游呢
Look who's lost in space.
有笔吗
Got a pen?
你有不带骷髅的东西吗
You got anything that doesn't have skulls in it?
你别说 还真没有
As a matter of fact, I don't.
这是爱因斯坦的狭义相对论
Einstein's theory of spatial relativity.
我把它优化了
But we have made it better.
信不信由你
Believe it or not,
贡纳嗑上那些化学品之前
before Gunner became chemically unbalanced,
是麻省理工的高材生
he went to MIT
还是化学工程的硕士
and had a Master's degree in chemical engineering.
没想到这家伙还有脑子
This idiot actually had a brain, can you believe that?
那后来呢
What happened?
他辍学当保安了
He quit to be a bouncer.
那时候我喜欢上一个迪斯科舞厅的舞女
I wanted to get close to this girl and dance at this disco.
是啊 她最后竟然甩了你
And I can't believe she dumped you.
你会吗
Wouldn't you?
当然会
I would, yeah.
能出去聊聊吗
Can we talk outside?
行啊 我们走
Yeah, sure, let's go!
怎么说好呢
How do I put this...
你就直说吧 没关系
Just be straight up, honest.
我觉得
I feel, uh...
我说不清这种感觉
I'm not sure what I feel.
这种生活 不适合你 是吗
This life... It's not for you, is it?
以前挺适合
I thought it was.
谢谢你让我加入团队
You gave me a chance to be one of you,
我一直很敬佩你
you got my respect forever.
我也很敬佩你
And you got my respect too.
你怎么打算
What are you gonna do?
我想干完这个月
I'd like to finish out the month.
然后去找我女朋友
Then I wanna go meet up my girlfriend.
她是哪儿人
Where's she from?
她 她是法国人
She's, uh, she's French.
我们两个是在阿富汗认识的
Believe it or not I met her at Afghanistan,
她是个护士
she was a nurse.
一定很会照顾人
That comes in handy.
对 她人特别好
Yeah. You'd like her.
我愿意为她做任何事
You know, she's the kind of person you'd wanna do things for.
我干这一行就是因为收入高
That's why I took this job because the money's great...
这样我就能给她买她想要的东西
Now I can afford to get whatever that she deserves.
我觉得她就是我的另一半
It's one of those things that just feels right.
和她在一起的时候
I mean, you know when you could be with someone
我们都不用说什么
and you don't even have to talk.
就能知道彼此心意
You already know what they're thinking.
你能理解吗
You ever had that?
是的
Sure.
希望你不会当我是逃兵
I don't want you to think that I'm deserting you.
不 听着
No, lissten...
如果我像你这么年轻的话
If I had to do it all over again at your age,
我也会这么做
I'd do what you're doing.
再进去喝两杯
Why don't you freshen up that beer.
好的
Alright.
巴尼·罗斯
Barney Ross.
找我干嘛 教堂
What do you want from me, Church?
你的记性不太好吧 巴尼
Not too good on the memory category are you, Barney?
你上次帮我干活
You made a deal with me.
我们有言在先的
You gave me your word.
可结果呢 你毁了半个维兰纳岛
And you end up, blowing off half of Atlanta,
还把那个中情局特工打得满身窟窿
punching holes and a Bowie knife through a fellow CIA agent
虽说他是个坏蛋 可这也太过分了
even if he was a dirtbag.
不过最让我痛心的是
But what breaks my heart,
你竟然从我这儿偷了5百万美元
is that you stole 5 million dollars from me.
就凭你干的这些事
And for all this male-patterned badness
我可以把你丢进关塔那摩监狱
I gotta put you in the deepest,
最深最黑暗的牢房里
darkest hole in Gitmo.
永不见天日
No sunlight.
可我没这么做
But I kept you out.
谢谢
Why?
因为我知道总有一天你要还这笔账的
Because I knew the day would come when you were gonna pay me back.
那一天已经到了
Today is that day.
说下去
Keep talking.
有一架中国飞机在噶扎克附近的山区被人击落
Chinese plane got shot down over the mountains near a hellhole called Gazak.
是吗 谁干的
Yeah, who shot it down?
你猜猜看
Take a guess.
飞机上的保险箱里有一样东西
Aboard that plane is a safe carrying something
你不用知道它是什么
you don't need to know about.
这东西绝不能落到坏人手里
All you need to know is you can't let it fall onto the wrong hands.
我要你赶在其他人之前
Now you're gonna get in there,
找到保险箱 把里面的东西
you're gonna get the contents of that safe,
给我带回来
you're gonna bring it to me.
对你来说小菜一碟
Should be a walk in the park for you.
我们就两清了
And then we're even.
这个以后再说
You get that?
那个保险箱非常高级
The safe in that plane is very high-tech.
密码每隔120秒自动更换一次
The access code changes every 120 seconds,
如果输入错误密码 它就会爆炸
you use the wrong code, it blows.
- 所以我们得让你 - 等等 等等
- We need to get... - Wait, wait!
你说我们 你和谁一起工作
We? Who's "we"? Who are you working with?
这不关你的事
That's none of your business.
就当做是某个公司吧
Let's just call our host The Corporation..
明白吗 我会派一个负责处理这种情况的专家
Alright? They're sending along a pro,
跟你们一起去
who specializes in this type of situation.
- 她叫麦琪·张 - 女的
- Her name is Maggy Chan. - A woman?
一般叫这个名字的都是女人 对
That usually goes along with the name Maggy, yeah.
没门
Forget it.
她能照顾好自己
She can handle herself.
不过我要说清楚
But let me be clear:
如果她出了什么事
If anything happens to her,
手指头有肉刺 或者受伤了
She gets hanged there, she gets hurt,
或者被欺负了
she gets roughed up,
只要她回来时和去之前有什么不一样
she doesn't come back in exactly the same condition she went in,
你和你手下那帮混蛋就会从地球上消失
you and your little gang of psychotic mutts will never be seen again.
这一点 我可以保证
And that, I promise you.
我这个人不太会当保姆
I don't make a very good babysitter.
别小看自己
You sound so sure.
你会成为一个称职的保姆的
You're gonna make a very good babysitter.
7点准时到
Be there at 7.
嗨 我是麦琪·张
Hey. I'm Maggy Chan.
你是巴尼·罗斯吗
You Barney Ross?
对
Yeah.
教堂跟你说过我了
Mr. Church told you about me?
他说你非要跟着去
He said you wanna tag along.
不是 我是去帮忙
Help, not tag along.
摩托车不错
Nice motorcycle.
那个地方很陌生 不知道会发生什么
Where we're going, as you know, we don't know what to expect.
是定做的
Is it custom?
我觉得你跟我们去是个错误
I think it's a mistake, you coming along.
自己改装的
Build it yourself?
对 自己改装的
Yeah, I built it myself.
你在耍我吗 麦琪
Are you playing games with me, Maggy?
没有
No.
你不会是在耍我吧
Are you playing games with me?
教堂说了你的顾虑
Church told me what you said.
我精通格斗
I'm combat-proficient.
用不着什么保姆
I don't need a babysitter.
那我们几点出发
So, when do we leave?
早上5点
0500.
很高兴认识你
Nice meeting you.
(阿尔巴尼亚 噶扎克山区)
她喜欢我
She's into me.
她讨厌你
She ain't.
瞧着
Watch this.
要是她出了什么事
You know if something happens to her,
责任都是我们的
it's coming back on us.
你怎么不先问问我的意见
You ever think to ask me for my opinion?
我都跟你说了10遍了
I told you 10 times before,
我没有别的选择 除非你想蹲监狱
I didn't have a choice unless you don't mind going to jail.
看来教堂吓住你了
Yeah, well, church intimidated you.
- 是吗 - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
又是你那个水性杨花的女朋友吧
Is that the woman-you-can-never-fully-trust calling again?
总有一天我会捅死你
Yeah, I will stab you one day.
嗨 宝贝 对 我当然在想你
Hey, baby. Yeah, of course I'm thinking about you.
除了你 我还能想谁呢
What else is there to think about?
没救了
Hopeless.
嗨
Hey.
你当过兵 对吗
You're in the army, right?
看得出来
I can tell.
是的 长官 当了3年
Yes, ma'am. 3 years.
最后一次在阿富汗的库纳尔省
Last tour was Afghanistan.
为什么不干了
Didn't like it anymore?
这个说来话长了
It's a long story.
说出来听听吧
I would like to hear it.
好吧
Alright.
我 我学的是狙击
I, uh, was trained as a sniper...
他们想让我当教官 可我
and an instructor too but...
更想去战斗 去参加行动
I just really wanna mix it up, you know, the action bit.
有一次我们被困在一个该死的山谷里
One time, we were stuck out in this hellhole valley.
30多个敌人从山上的房子里向我们开火
About 30 Taliban opened up from these houses in the hills above us.
我们有8个人困在那儿
They got about 8 of us pinned down bad.
于是我呼叫炮火支援
So I called in for artillery support
可是上尉不同意
but, "no way", says the captain.
他不想伤及当地居民
Didn't want to endanger the locals.
我们只好分散开 有的躲进沟里
So we scattered, some crawled through a ditch, some,
有的跳进干枯的河床 可是
through a dry riverbed and the rest bailed, but...
我们还困在杀伤区里
We were still stuck in the killzone.
我们交战了
And we battled for...
大概3小时吧
I don't know, 3 hours?
最后终于来了一架阿帕奇直升机 掩护我们
And finally an apache gunship chopper showed up to provide air cover.
敌人打退了 可是
Scattered the hajis but..
我发现四个战友死在沟里
The smoke clears and four of my squad are dead on the ditch
两个死在河床上
and two on the riverbed.
是的 我当时很愤怒
Yeah, it's bad, sick...
他们死得多冤呐
All dead for nothing.
知道吗 更让我受不了的是
Do you know the most... screwed up thing of all?
那天晚上我回到基地
When I got back to base that night,
发现他们把我
I found out that they had shot...
我收养的流浪狗给打死了
This stray dog that I adopted.
指挥官下令除掉基地里的所有动物
Commander's order's to get rid of all animals on the base.
好像我们这一天下来杀得还不够似的
I mean, think, we had enough damn shooting for one day, you know?
就因为这样 我决定离开那儿
Anyway.. I, figured it was time to move on.
正巧他们在招人 我就来了
I heard these guys were looking for someone and here I am.
应答器有反应了吗
You got that transponder?
有 目标在西北方向15公里
Yes, apparently, 15 km northwest.
好的
Okay.
喂 亲爱的
Hello, darling..
我有点忙
We're a little busy...
我们走 快完成任务
Right, let's move, wanna be outta here fast.
越快越好
The sooner, the better.
- 比利小子 - 是
- Billy the Kid. - Yeah?
今天靠你了 去选据点
Today's your lucky day, you get to take point.
很荣幸 长官
My pleasure, sir.
了不起
Impressive.
别挂
Hold on.
你当年能跑这么快吗
Remember when you could do that?
忘了 你呢
No. Do you?
这根本不算什么
I'd run away if I needed to.
是吗
Really?
往下看
Look down.
往下看 看见了吗 凭你这短腿
Look down.. You see what I see? Short legs.
我赌一千块你追不上
A thousand bucks, you can't catch him.
去啊 闪电侠
Come on, Flash!
我今天没空
I'm a little busy.
我知道
Oh, yeah.
飞机残骸在山脚下
Found the wreckage, spotted a hill, sir!
慢点 比利 给我们留点面子
Slow down, Billy. You're making us look bad.
你说什么
Say again, over?
别装傻
You heard.
收到 我会慢一点
Roger that, slowing down.
非常感谢
We appreciate it.
还有一些 在山另一边
Rest of the plane's over the hill, sir.
干得好 比利
Good work, Billy!
看来这些人的运气不太好
Looks like somebody had a bad day.
你们去右边
You guys, get to the right!
一群饿狼
Piss off, you roamers.
比利 去上面找有利位置
Alright Billy, you get a vantage point up there.
他们手里有狼毛
There's fur in the hands.
狼群来之前他们还没死
This guy was alive 'til the wolves got to him.
小心点
Be careful.
是这儿吗
Is this it?
对 就在里面
Yes, it's here.
凯撒 你进来
Caesar! I need you in here!
你抓住这个
Caesar grab a hold of this thing,
里面好像有弹簧
I think it's spring loaded.
圣诞 钩住它
Lee, hook it on.
我数到三 大家就拉
Now on the count of three let's pull it back.
准备
Ready?
一 二 三
One, two, three!
我们拉不住了
We can't hold this!
坚持住
You have to.
(上传数据 已连接)
(接收密码)
快点 麦琪
Come on, Maggy!
(信号中断 协议错误)
出问题了
Something's wrong.
怎么了
What?
炸弹的引爆器启动了
The explosive timer's triggered.
有多久
How long?
54秒
54 seconds.
现在跑还来得及
If we leave now, we'll make it!
麦琪 别管它了
Maggy, let it go!
不 我能弄好
No, I can do it!
(手动输入)
快走 麦琪
Come on, Maggy!
嗨 怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
(重输密码)
她触发了引爆器
She tripped the detonator, stay back!
我快抓不住了
I'm losing my grip..
挺住 不然她会死的
You just, hold it..
(密码确认)
快出来 麦琪
Get out, Maggy!
搞定
Got it!
幸亏有我在
Lucky I was here..
我想也是
Just thinking that.
对不起 不过它真的很重要
I'm sorry, it's important I get this.
我知道 看来你也是个不要命的
You got guts, no common sense.
走吧
But guts. Come on.
搞定了 任务完成 我们撤
It's alright, we got it, let's go.
你挺厉害
You're strong.
比利 下来吧 我们走
Billy. Come on down, we're outta here.
怎么了
What happened?
那小妞真猛 还好我心脏够强
That woman is crazy, but I got a good pump.
你不想知道里面装了什么吗
Aren't you curious about what's inside the case?
不想 我只希望教堂别再烦我
No, I just wanna get Church off our backs.
比利小子
Billy the Kid!
他在哪儿
Where the hell is he?
比利
Billy!
放下武器
Drop your weapons.
没门
No way.
不放
Ain't happening.
No?
你们确定吗
Are you sure?
对不起 长官 我中了埋伏
I'm sorry, sir, they were waiting.
快把武器放下
Drop the weapons now.
别听他的
Don't do it.
他是个坚强的士兵
He's a strong soldier.
我们看看他有多坚强
Let's see how strong he is.
动手
Do it.
不
No!
你们别听他的
Don't do nothing he says!
不要说话
Don't talk.
你不该说话
You should not speak.
我要宰了他
I'm gonna kill him.
我一开火 他的头
When I fire, his head,
就没了
will be gone.
我数到三
Three seconds.
别交出武器 你们不用管我
Don't give your weapons, you don't owe me anything!
一
One...
二
Two...
别听他的 他会杀了你们
Don't do this! They'll kill everyone.
他会杀了比利
He's gonna kill him.
我数到三了
放下武器
Drop them!
真让人感动 这个是个明智的选择
I'm impressed. Very good use of intelligence.
大家都别动 我们很快就能完事
Everybody stay calm, we'll be done soon.
然后我们就会走
And then we will be on our way.
把它给我
Bring me that knife.
这是什么标志
What's this symbol?
我喜欢它
I like symbol.
这是山羊的标志
This is the symbol of the goat.
它是 魔鬼的宠物
The pet... of Satan.
据说是
They say..
你们拿了属于我的盒子
You have a case that belongs to me.
是吗
Does it?
是的 连命也是我的
Yes. Like your lives.
盒子丢了 不在他那儿
It's lost. He doesn't have it.
最后一次机会 把盒子给我
Last time, the case.
不然
Or you will force me...
我就
To cut...
把他的心脏挖出来
His heart out.
来吧 你这个混蛋
Do it, you piece of shit!
等等
Wait!
让我来
Let me have it.
嗨
Hey!
你叫我
You talking to me?
把它捡起来
Pick it up.
交给我
Hand it to me.
你自己去捡
Humiliate yourself.
你说什么
What was that?
你听到了
You heard...
把它捡起来
Now pick it up..
好好放到我手里
hand it to me nicely.
不然你会跟他一样
Or you will get what he got.
捡吧
Do it, Lee.
你不会有事的
You'll be alright, buddy.
尊重是最重要的
Respect is everything.
没有尊重 我们就是凡人
Without respect, we're just people...
卑微的凡人
common, shitty people.
对不起 长官
I'm sorry, sir.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
接下来呢
Now what?
我们都是战士
We're both fighting men.
我尊重你们
And I respect that.
作为战士 不应该像羊一样被宰掉
And fighting men, they don't deserve to be killed like sheep.
不过
But...
你们得学会尊重
Respect, must be taught.
现在脸朝下 趴在地上
Lie down with your face on the ground,
直到我们离开
until we leave.
别想挑战我
Don't challenge me.
趴下
Get down.
起来
Up!
你怕我吗
Are you afraid of me?
不
No.
我不怕
I'm not!
你应该怕
You should be.
- 对不起 - 别说话 比利
- I'm dying. - Don't talk, Billy.
把绳子解开
Cut his hands loose.
有封信在 我口袋里
Letter, in my pocket.
好的 我拿到了
Okay kid, I got it.
拿到了
I got it..
真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry..
我知道
I blame you.
盒子里装了什么
What was in the case?
一台电脑 存了矿山的蓝图
A computer blueprint of a mine.
矿山
A mine?
什么矿山
What mine?
俄罗斯人在那座矿山里藏了5吨武器级别的钚
The Russians stole nearly 5 tons of weapons grade Plutonium.
冷战后那座矿废弃了
The mine was abandoned after the Cold War.
没人知道这事
No one knows it's there.
蓝图上标明了那些原料的位置
The blueprints show where the Plutonium is stored.
我们想防止它落到坏人手里
We have to stop it before it gets in the wrong hands.
看来你们没成功 对吗
Guess that didn't happen, did it?
他们为了造炸弹 杀了那孩子
This kid died so that some dirtbag could make bombs.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
我比你更遗憾
Not as sorry as I am.
好好埋葬他
Let's take care of him.
亲爱的苏菲娅
"Dear Sophia.
我真希望除了想念你 我还能找到别的事情做
I wish I could find something different to do besides just missing you...
可我找不到
but I can't.
队员们都对我很好
The team's treating me good.
我们互相照应
We got each other's backs.
记住 不管我发生什么事
And I want you to know that wherever I end up,
我都希望你能好好的
I'll be wanting the very best for you.
如果奇迹发生我还能回来
And if some miracle happens and I come back again,
希望 还能做你的爱人 爱你的比利
I hope I'm still your man. Much love, Billy."
为什么会这样
Why is it that one of us...
我们当中最想活着最应该活下去的人却死了
who wants to live the most, who deserves to live the most, dies.
而那些本该死的人 却还活着
And the ones that deserve to die, keep on living.
上天要告诉我们什么
What's the message in that?
你有什么计划
What's the plan?
追踪他 找到他 宰了他
Track 'em, find 'em, kill 'em.
CJ1492 听到呼叫请回答
CJ 1492 come up, requesting response immediately.
这个笨蛋是谁
Is this Bozo?
CJ1492 这是安全频道 能听到吗
CJ 1492 this is a secure airwave, do you read?
什么事
What's this about?
怎么花了这么长时间 巴尼·罗斯
What's taking so long, Barney Ross?
这任务对你来说轻而易举
This should have been a walk in the park for you guys.
盒子在哪儿
Where's the case?
不在我手里
Don't have it.
我警告过 你如果这次搞砸了 你们会有什么结果
I warned you what would happen to you mutts if you pulled this shit again.
一个好人为了这个盒子牺牲了
A good man died trying to get that case.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry about that.
真的吗
Oh, yeah?
是的 我真的感到很遗憾
Yes, as a matter of fact, I am.
不过那地方难免会发生这种事 不是吗
Look, this sort of situation comes with the territory, wouldn't you say?
复仇也是难免的
And so is payback.
听着 教堂 你是个只敢在幕后
You know, Church, you're that kind of guy that pulls his strings
操纵别人去干脏活的胆小鬼
and everyone else does your dirty work
因为你没胆量自己去干
because you've never had the guts to do it yourself.
我不干了
We're done.
长官 我们碰到麻烦了
Sir, we got a problem.
挖掘速度越来越慢
The digging has slowed down.
好多人死了
Too many are dying,
都是累死的
and exhausted.
他太累了
He's tired.
还有人觉得累吗
Anybody else tired?
再找些工人来
Get more workers.
村里的男人已经全都抓来了
Already taken most of the men from the villages.
那就抓剩下的
Get all the rest.
女人 孩子 全都抓来
Women, children, all of them.
给我看
Show me.
这下知道它在哪儿了
Now we know where it is.
不错 不错
Right, right.
好的 我知道怎么做了
Ok... I know what to do.
很好 三天之内把原料全都运出去
Good, I want the Plutonium all in three days.
三天
Three days?
有个买家愿意以每公斤四百万收购
I have people, ready to pay four million a kilo, now.
三天之内必须搞定
Three days. No more.
明白
Understood.
你很聪明 你想想看 只要六磅这种原料
Yes, smart, imagine if six pounds of pure Plutonium
就足以改变整个世界的格局
is powerful enough to change the balance of the world.
那五吨原料可以干什么
So imagine what 5 tons would do.
很有意思吧
It's very interesting.
(信号丢失)
有点不对劲
Something's happening.
怎么了
What?
信号中止了 他们在地下
The transmissions stopped. They are underground
那就在这儿r降落
I'm putting it down right here.
快点 大家动作快点 我们得走了
Come on, let's hustle, hustle! We gotta move!
圣诞
Christmas! Come on. Lee.
我说你什么时候能把它修好
Do you even know what the hell you're doing?
五分钟 耐心点 别老催我
Five minutes. Don't get your knickers in a twist.
好吧
Yeah.
又有一辆货车 可能是他们的
That transport truck, could be one of theirs.
我们过去看看
Let's check this place out.
不要用枪
No shooting.
用经典装备
Classics?
对
Yeah.
我早就想用这个了
I've been dying to use these.
我们要打出情报来
We'll beat the truth out of them.
麦琪 告诉大家在车里等着
Maggy, tell the guys to wait in the truck.
好的
Okay.
- 他们都在 - 是啊
- They're here. - Yeah.
生意不错吗
You speak English?
- 他个头有点大 - 那你
- He's slightly gigantic. - Shut up.
我说说而已
Just saying.
- 他的个头的确很大 - 我就说嘛
- He's really gigantic. - I said that!
你们来这儿想干嘛
找死吗 知道我们是谁吗
还是这个好用
Little bit of classics.
从他们身上打出情报来然后就走
I say we beat some info out of these guys and get moving.
我没意见
Sounds good to me.
从那个矮子开始
Let's start with the midget.
等等 伙计们 我用更简单的办法
Calm down, boys. I can get them to talk
让他们开口
with much less effort.
你要干嘛 帮他们修脚
What are you gonna do, give them a pedicure?
这有点变态
That's a little sick.
圣诞 你把卡车发动起来
Christmas, I need you to hotwire that truck
回飞机上取点武器过来
and go back to the plane and get the weapons.
你干嘛不叫那个奶酪头去
She get one of those if she sends you to do it.
别发牢骚
Stop complaining.
我真该一拳砸开你的头
I should have bashed one of these up on your skull-
情况怎么样
How did it go?
搞定了 我们走
We're on, let's move!
他们自称是桑族人
They call themselves Sangs,
这些人控制着山区东面的一切
they say they control everything east of the mountains.
抢劫 绑架 暗杀 什么都干
Robbery, kidnapping, assassinations.
就像雇佣兵一样
Basically a cartel for hire.
你能听懂他们的语言
How do you know the language?
简单 半听半猜
Easy, put it together.
它介于乌克兰语和保加利亚语之间
It's a cross between Ukraine and Bulgarian dialect.
我很牛吧
Impressed?
还行
A little.
圣诞
Christmas!
干嘛
What?
你吼什么
Why are you yelling?
因为你给了我一个垃圾活
Because you gave me the shit job, that's why.
等我回来我一枪毙了你
I'll shoot you in the face when I see you.
你在哪儿
Where are you?
在你60岁高龄的破飞机边上
The 60-year old death-trap you call a plane.
怎么花了这么久
What's taking you so long?
桥坏了 路标也没有
Because there's bridges out, signs missing,
我在破土路上颠了7个小时
I've been driving in these damn roads for the last 7 hours!
牢骚发完了吗
You done complaining?
谢谢你的慰问
Thanks for the sympathy.
这里很诡异
This is weird.
像家一样
It's like home.
难怪这么诡异
Figures...
这到底是什么地方
What the hell is this place?
我觉得是前苏联的军事基地
I believe it's an old Soviet army base.
八十年代冷战时期
Probably used in the '80s,
使用的
The Cold War.
当年他们一定是在这儿进行专门针对美国的军事演习
They most likely staged maneuvers and practiced attacks against the US here.
有什么是你不知道的吗
Is there anything you don't know?
(雷氏披萨饼店)
太棒了 我就喜欢老字号的披萨
Great, just what I need, 50-year old pizza.
(百事可乐 量更多味更美)
我们就在这儿过夜
We'll bed down here for the night.
这东西难吃死了 你的怎么样
This tastes like shit. How's yours?
我做的通心粉味道错不了
Can't complain about Rigatoni.
要未雨绸缪 伙计们
Dine ahead, fellas.
这是很重要的
That's all I have to say.
我说 如果你知道自己明天会死
Hell, what if you knew you were gonna die tomorrow?
最后一顿会吃什么
What would your last meal be?
只能选一种
One choice.
就一种
One choice?
你会选麦片粥吧
Probably cereal for you, huh?
麦片粥有什么不好
Well, what the hell is wrong with cereal?
太没创意
It's cliche.
你可以搞创意
You gotta be original, you know,
如果你有创造精神
if you were an original, broad-thinking man,
没准能发明一种耳朵形状的麦片
you'd probably come up with some special cereal
取名叫耳麦 就跟你的耳朵一样
like Eareal, you know, just like your ear...
把它们泡在牛奶里 这样你就
Pour milk on those suckas and just lay it in,
什么也听不见了
and you don't wanna eat shit.
我要声明 我听力很好 不比你差
For the record, my hearing is 20/20.
巴尼
Barney?
我选甜甜圈这种垃圾食品
Donuts and most food that kills you.
太深奥了
That's deep, man.
是吗 你这么想
I think so.
麦琪
Maggy?
如果是我 会选香酥鸭
Crispy aromatic duck.
配上苏梅酱
With plum sauce.
非常性感
Very sexy.
意大利菜也不错
But I like Italian, too.
我觉得意大利菜不怎么样
I'm starting to think Italian's overrated.
怎么不问我
What about me?
我最喜欢的瑞典菜是
My very Swedish dinner would be...
夏天的
Baby seal,
小海豹肉
and whale ass...
和鲸鱼屁股
in the summer.
不过我一直很想尝尝中国菜
Bu I'd really die, for some Chinese.
那你就等着饿死吧
Then you're gonna starve to death.
行了 睡觉吧
Alright, sweet dreams.
嗨 巴尼 我还没吃完呢
Hey, Barney, I'm not done eating man.
- 能问你件事吗 - 行 说吧
- Can I ask you something? - Sure, go ahead.
为什么看到我这么紧张
Why are you so nervous around me?
我不是紧张 麦琪
I don't get nervous, Maggy.
那是什么
What is it then?
我喜欢保持一点距离
I just like keeping a distance.
是因为你不想再认识新朋友吗
Is it because you don't want to know any more people?
这么说吧 跟我亲近的人
Let's just say that bad things have happened to people
容易遇到不好的事情
I've come in close to.
这种心态可不好啊
Not a good way to live.
我知道
I know.
还在想那个死去的小伙子
Do you think about the young man who died?
一直在想
All the time.
可你很少提起他
You don't talk about him much.
我们就是这样面对死亡的
No, 'cause it's how we deal with death.
我们改变不了 只能淡化它
Can't change what it is so we keep it light
直到黑暗越来越近
until it's time to get dark.
把我们彻底吞没
And then we get pitch black.
明白吗
Understand?
我明白
I understand.
晚安
Goodnight.
晚安 麦琪
Goodnight, Maggy.
我对天发誓 他要是再打下去我就毙了他
I swear to God, if he won't stop snoring I'm gonna shoot him.
贡纳
Gunner!
你叫我
You riding?
我知道这个问题很蠢
I know it's a stupid question,
你煮的咖啡还有多的吗
I don't suppose you have any more of that coffee?
只够一个人喝的
Only makes one cup.
是啊 我猜也是
Yeah, that's what I figured.
听着
Listen up!
那些人说桑族人基本上都在这个地方
This guy said that a congregation of Sangs are probably in this area.
集中在东面
Concentrated east.
我们要去那儿
So that's where we're going.
10分钟后出发
We're out of here in 10 minutes.
大家快点 做好准备
Be ready, do what you got to do.
那儿 注意警戒
伙计们 我们有麻烦了
Guys, we got problem.
趴下
Get down!
趴下 趴下
Get down! Get down!
我们得离开这儿
We got to get out of here!
快
Go!
快 快 快
Go, go, go!
快点 快点 快点
Go, go, go, go, go!
走
Go!
省点弹药
Save your ammo.
你在哪儿呢
Where the hell are you?
就快到了
I'm almost there!
怎么回事 那是枪声吗
What's going on, are those shots?
对
Yeah!
出了什么事
What's happening?
我们被桑族人包围了
The sang's got us pinned down.
挺得住吗
Can you hold them off?
有辆坦克也许行
Yeah, maybe with a tank.
噢 见鬼
Oh, shit.
怎么
What?
他们有辆坦克 走 走 快走
They got a tank. Come on, come on!
我们走 快
Let's roll, come on!
没子弹了
I'm out.
我还有一发 试试吧
One left. Why not?
这是谁干的
Hey who did that?
不是我 我没弹药了
Not me, I'm out!
怎么回事
What just happened?
附近好像有个狂人
Somebody got a little carried away.
真是太狂了
Looks that way.
开枪的人在哪儿
Where're the shooters?
不知道 不过他要想杀我们
I don't know, but if they had wanted us dead,
我们早死了
we'd be dead.
巴尼
Barney.
大家别慌
Don't freak out.
世界真小 巴尼
Small world, huh, Barney?
布克
Booker.
听说你死了
Rumor has it, you were dead.
是啊 我也听说了
Yeah, I heard that too.
你最近怎么样
So how's life treating you?
挺好的
Been better.
这是你一个人干的
You did all this?
我一向单干 你应该知道
I fight solo, I thought you knew that?
对 我听说过 可一直不信
Yeah, I heard but I didn't buy it.
现在信了吧
Well now you do.
- 你的团队 - 对
- This your team? - Yeah.
贡纳 托尔·罗德 强壮凯撒 还有麦琪
Gunner, Toll Road, Hale Caesar and Maggy.
布克
Booker?
你就是他们说的孤狼
You're the one people call the "Lone Wolf"?
我以前很凶狠
I've been called that.
现在温柔多了
But I have mellowed.
没看出来
Not that much.
我还听有人说
I heard another rumor
你被一条眼镜王蛇咬了
that you were bitten by a King Cobra?
对 没错 经过长达五天的痛苦挣扎
Yeah, I was. But after five days of agonizing pain,
那条蛇死了
The cobra died.
布克 很高兴见到你
Hey Booker, great to see you.
你们怎么会来这种鸟不拉屎的地方
So how'd you wind up in this godforsaken place?
我们被桑族人伏击了
Yeah, we got ambushed by Sang
在东边100公里的地方 他们杀了我的人
about a 100 km east of here, killed one of my men,
- 一个年轻人 - 啊 我很遗憾
- a young kid. - Yeah, sorry to hear that.
嗯
Yeah.
那些桑族人是最无耻的渣滓
The Sans are the lowest form of scum.
干掉他们是件好事
Shooting them have been a good business.
他们的头儿是谁
You know who the leader is?
一个叫维莱恩的家伙
Yeah a guy named Vilain.
维莱恩
Vilain?
那家伙完全控制着这个地区
Yeah, he pretty much controls everything in this area.
如果你们想活着出去 得找人帮忙
You're gonna need more men if you'd expect to get out alive.
你能帮忙吗
Can you help out?
对不起 巴尼 我一个人干
Sorry, Barney. I work alone.
我明白
I understand.
今天谢谢你
Thanks for showing up.
别客气
My pleasure.
嗨 巴尼 前面有个村子
Hey Barney, there's a village down the road.
那里都是好人
There are good people,
他们痛恨桑族人
and they hate the sangs.
没准能帮你
Maybe they can help out.
谢谢
Thanks!
玩得开心
Happy hunting!
出了什么事
What happened?
我还活着
I'm still alive.
算你走运 怎么回事
It's a matter of opinion, what did I miss?
我在路上告诉你
I'll tell you all about it on the way.
来吧 把武器装上车
Come on guys, unload these weapons.
今年圣诞好像来得特别晚呐
Looks like Christmas came way late this year.
我知道你想我
Yeah I love you, too.
很高兴能再见到你
Well, I'm happy to see you.
总算碰上个识货的人了
Finally. Somebody with class.
这一定就是布克说的那个村子
It's got to be the town that Booker was talking about.
我可以在这样的地方养老
I could retire to a place like this.
空气新鲜 没有压力 再养几个孩子
Clean air, no stress, raise some kids.
我说 麦琪 我真的想在这种地方养老
You know, Maggy, I could retire to a pace like this.
别胡说八道了
You are so full of shit.
快下车
Out! out! out!
他们打得也太糟了
They're missing us by a mile.
把枪放下
Put down guns.
这是不可能的
That's not happening!
他们瞄准的地方最安全
Safest place is in front of their gun.
我们要开枪了
We will shoot you!
不
No!
等等
Wait.
我们是来帮忙的
These guys are here to help.
我们想帮你们
They want to help.
就算是你们俩 在这儿也会有艳遇的
Even you two rejects could get lucky around here.
- 真的 - 我不信
- You think? - I doubt it.
别废话
Do you mind?
你们是谁
Who you are?
- 我们是美国人 - 谁说的
- We're American. - Since when?
瑞典人
Swedish.
印第安人
Blackford.
中国人
Chinese.
一群弱智
Retards.
说完了
Are you done?
你们想干嘛
What do you want?
我们是来解决桑族人的
We are here to take care of The Sangs.
好吧
Okay.
进屋说吧
Come inside.
来吧
Come on.
我以为你们是来抓孩子的
This is who we'd think you've come for.
我们死也要保护他们
This is who we will die for.
一开始那些人跟我们说有好工作 工资很高
First, they told us there'd be good jobs, good money.
有些人去了 去了就再没回来
Some went, but nobody come back.
他们又找了些人去
They come for more.
他们说只要有新的人去
They say as soon as our men go to job,
之前那些人就能回来
the others come home.
我丈夫去了
My husband goes.
过了很长时间 一直没音讯
For a long time we hear nothing.
后来
Then...
桑族人来村里把所有的男人都抓走了
the Sangs come and they take all of the rest of the men.
逼他们在矿山里干活
Force them to work in the mines.
隔壁村也是
Same in the next village.
附近村都是 他们抓走了我儿子
And the next, they take my sons.
现在就剩下这些小孩了
Now all that is left, are the very young.
那些家伙还会来抓人
And they will be back for them, too.
我知道的
I know this.
我们都知道
We all know this.
我们把孩子藏起来
So we hide them,
等那些人来
and we wait.
你们干嘛不走呢 离开这儿
Why don't you just move on? Leave.
这是我们的家
This is our home.
我们死也不会离开这里的
Our lives will be the last thing they'll take.
你们怎么会来这儿的
Tell us why you're here now.
找桑族人
We're tracking them.
能留下来
Can't you stay?
帮我们吗 看看那些孩子
And help? You saw the children!
桑族人会回来杀光他们
Soon they'll be damned and they'll kill them all.
我们也有账要和他们算
We have our own business with them.
对不起
Sorry.
我们走
Let's go!
我觉得她们坚持不了多久的
I don't think they're gonna last here much longer.
他们知道这一点
I think they know that.
我们不做点什么吗
So we're not gonna do anything about it?
我有个主意
I have an idea.
以你的性格一定会喜欢
And with your ego I think you're gonna love it.
- 我的性格 - 你的性格
- My ego? - Your ego.
- 我的什么性格 - 你很自恋
- What you mean my ego? - You got a big ego.
你很自恋
You got a big ego.
你才自恋呢
Check your ego out!
得了 你这家伙简直自恋到极点
Please, your ego is like the size of a dinosaur.
自恋狂
It's huge.
找到了
We got it.
我们找到钚原料了
We found the Plutonium.
伊娃 桑族人来了 通知所有人
Eva. The Sangs are coming! Warn everyone!
桑族人来了
搜查所有房屋
Search all the houses!
注意警戒
Keep on looking!
快跑 快跑
Lari! Lari!
你们几个 去那边搜
动作快点
主啊 他们已经互相选择了对方
求你保佑他们的爱情纯洁 他们的誓言真诚
赋予这爱情耶稣的名字
他们在哪儿 神父
Show us where the kid is, priest.
别多管闲事
And get out of our way.
现在我以上帝的名义
By the power vested in me...
宣布你和这把刀永结同心
I now pronounce you man and knife.
还有一个
One more!
下地狱吧
Rest in pieces.
这是最后一个
Is this the last one?
对
Yes.
很好
Good.
仓库清空了
Chambers are cleared.
不许留活口
Now a good sentence.
全都处理掉
You bury them all.
我看到十多个守卫
I see about a dozen guards.
轻武器 还有几把重型机枪
Light weapons, couple of badass 50 cals.
不止这些
Worse,
他们还有反坦克装备
anti-tank devices.
我们的卡车根本冲不进矿区
There's no way our trucks will get through that minefield.
我知道这问题很傻
Look, I know this is a stupid question,
你有什么不是送死的计划吗
but you got any ideas so we won't get killed?
倒是有几个
I got a few I'm thinking about.
炸开花
Boom time?
Boom time!
发现目标
Target in sight!
宝贝 等不及了
Baby wants to travel!
开火
Fire!
- 够刺激吧 - 开火
- Rock and roll! - Fire!
投弹完毕
Bombs away!
都跪下
系好安全带
Tighten up.
现在什么情况
What's happening now?!
混乱
Chaos!
你不会是要真的要这么干吧
You're not doing what I think you're doing!
你猜对了
Yeah, I am!
来吧
Let's do it!
快点 快走
Come on, let's move!
你得换架飞机了
You're gonna need a new plane.
我们很快就能回家了
We'll be home soon...
- 我们来晚了 - 怎么
- We are too late! - What?!
原料运走了
The Plutonium is gone!
要爆炸了
To explode!
快 快 快 快离开这儿
Come on, come on, get out of here!
- 快 快 快 - 快走 大家快走
- Go, go, go. - Move it, move it!
快离开这儿
Come on, get out of here!
得在这儿待一会儿了
We're gonna be here a while.
怎么会这样
Doesn't seem right.
没想到结局是这样的
Going out this chickenshit way?
是啊 糟透了
Yeah, something like that.
嗨 还没完呢 伙计们 我有个主意
It ain't over yet, kids. I got a plan.
大家都冷静
Everybody calm down.
磷酸盐岩
Phosphate rock.
他要干嘛
What is he doing?
大概是想做炸弹
Probably making a bomb.
开玩笑吧
You serious?
你问他啊
Ask him.
你在干嘛
What you doing, Gunner?
我在做炸弹 有问题吗
I'm making a bomb. You mind?
有文化的疯子
A maniac with brains.
真吓人
Scary.
磷酸盐岩 密度是1.852
Phosphate rock, got a density of 1.52,
熔点是摄氏44.2度
melting point 44.2 centigrade.
伙计们 给我点火药 快点
Guys! I want some gunpowder, fast!
给他 人家可是学化学工程的
Do it! The man's a chemical engineer, right?
还是富布莱特学者
And a full-pledged scholar.
倒进管子里
Pour it in the pipe.
这大个子没准开窍了
Big man might be onto something.
- 真的吗 - 也许不是
- You think? - Probably not.
估计没有
Probably not.
怎么这么慢 快点
Need some help with that, let's go!
给你 把自己炸了吧
Here you go, blow yourself up.
打火机
Lighter.
用完还我
I want that back.
大家都后退 声音会很响
Better get back! This is gonna be loud!
都后退
Get back!
好了 行了
Okay, alright, let's go!
好了
Alright!
不想把脑袋炸了 就退远点
Better turn around unless you want your heads blown up.
把耳朵堵上
Better cover your ears.
快点
Come on!
岩石一定是受潮了
All the phosphate's must've been damp.
是啊 没错
Yeah, right.
是你脑子受潮了
Or you suck.
我想也是
there's that.
别哭 贡纳
Don't cry, Gunner.
至少你敢想
You almost had an idea.
我回来了
I'm back!
你好啊 战壕
How you doing, Trench?
谢谢 太谢谢你们了
Oh, thank you.
不用谢
You're welcome.
罗占
皮拉尔
我们扯平了 对吗
We're even now, right?
对
Right.
回头见 战壕 多谢了
I'll be seeing you around, Trench. Thanks a lot.
别急 还没结束呢
Relax, it's not over yet.
什么
What?
好戏在后面
That's right.
你好吗 伙计
How you doing, pal?
我挺好的 教堂 你到这儿来干嘛
Pretty good, church, what're you doing here?
听说这儿有个聚会
Heard there's a party in town.
对 我的聚会
Yeah, but it's my party.
他一直这么自私吗
Has he always been this selfish?
一直都是
Always.
谢谢
Thanks.
你想不想干掉那个维莱恩
You wanna kick Vilain's ass or not?
带上你那些兄弟
Don't forget the little rascal!
快开
Move it.
让其他车直接开到飞机库里 快
Take the rest of the nukes to the hangar, now!
把原料都装上飞机
And get the Plutonium on the plane.
跟我来
Follow me.
我们要争取时间
We need to buy some time.
快走 走
Move move!
没子弹了
I'm out!
拖住他们
Hold them up. Go... move!
快 快 快走
Go.. go! Move!
- 好玩吧 - 是啊
- Fun, huh? - Yeah.
噢 他在那儿
Oh, there he is!
老大 快走
Let's go!
来吧
Yeah!
把他撕成碎片
Tear him apart!
我快没子弹了
I'm almost out!
我会回来的
I'll be back.
怎么每次都是你
You've been back enough.
这次我去
I'll be back.
什么意思嘛
Yippee-ki-yay.
还有谁会来 兰博吗
Who's next? Rambo?
再见
Good bye!
我们走
Let's go.
混蛋
Maggots.
发动引擎
Start the engine.
马上起飞
Get this thing in the air.
我要去赚钱了
I want to make some money!
快
Move!
战壕 快上来
Trench! Get in!
我的鞋都比这车大
My shoe is bigger than this car.
干掉他们
Shoot something!
来吧
Go!
(警报 携带武器 禁止通过)
准备直升机
Start the helicopter.
有位特殊客人要来
We have a special guest coming!
快点
Let's go!
快干掉他
Take care of him!
这边
This way!
经典就是经典
Can't beat the Classic.
巴尼
Barney!
你来这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
我一个人进去
Now I'm going there alone,
不管发生什么事都别进来
don't follow me no matter what, you understand?
明白吗
You understand?
明白
Yes.
如果门开了 出来的不是我 而是他
If that door opens up and I don't come out, and he does,
宰了他
you kill him.
我们来点戏剧性的
Let's make it more dramatic!
现在好多了
Now that's better!
我没子弹了
I'm out of bullets!
那是你的事
That's your problem.
不一定
Not really.
你是想杀人呢
You wanna kill me like a man?
还是想
Or you wanna kill me...
宰羊
like a sheep?
是把好刀
Nice knife.
我说
So...
你选哪个
What is it going to be?
杀人还是宰羊
Man or sheep?
你想单挑
You wanna man up?
我来陪你玩
I'll man you up.
你一定很想折磨我吧
You must want to hurt me bad.
我不会折磨你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我只想要你命
I'm gonna take your life.
来吧
Come..
这么快就完了
Over so soon?
我的本还没回来呢
I want my money's worth!
来啊 起来
Come on, get up!
马上就来
Coming right up!
味道好吗
Tastes good?
你跟我说话
Talking to me?
该收场了
Time to wrap this up!
太讽刺了
Ironic.
我们对战
Here we are, you and I.
而我 拿着你的刀
And your knife.
我会杀了你
You're going to die.
像杀他一样
Like him.
他叫什么名字
What was his name?
你们叫他什么
What did you call him?
他叫什么
What does it matter?
来啊 维莱恩
Come on, Vilain.
我才不怕你呢
Somebody's dying.
来啊 维莱恩
Come on! Vilain.
来啊 维莱恩 来啊
Come on, Vilain! Come on!
起来 维莱恩
Berdiri Vilain.
给我 起来
Get... up!
现在转过来
Now turn around.
转过来 小羊
Turn around, sheep!
怎么着
Now, what!?
他的名字叫比利
His name was Billy.
你会切火鸡吗
We oughta go to Turkey?
赢了
Did you win?
我想是的
I think so.
怎么证明
Well, where's the proof?
小心碰头
Head's up.
干得漂亮
Nice touch.
干得不错
It is a nice touch.
有点过了
A little extreme.
不过挺好
But nice.
虽然我不想提这事 伙计
As much as I hate to say this, Bam-Bam,
不过既然你们拿回了原料
now that we got control of the Plutonium,
我们扯平了
that makes us even.
很好
Good.
麦琪 你跟我们一起回去吗
So Maggy you'll be coming with us, then?
你自己考虑
When you're ready.
我只是想
So I just want..
他们有点孩子气
You're OK, just a little immature.
我不一定要走
I don't have to go.
如果你希望我留下 我就留下
If you want me to stay, I'll stay.
别忘了我还救了你这个保姆一命呢
And I did save a babysitter's life.
的确如此
That you did do.
我会给你带来好运
Maybe I'm good luck for you.
可我会给你带来厄运 我不想这样
But I can be bad luck for you and I can't allow that.
如果需要帮手
If you ever want help,
来找我 不然你死定了
call me. Or you're dead.
我会的
I'll do that.
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
走啊 你把活都干完了
Moving on, you killed all my business.
你不是一匹孤狼吗
I thought you were the "Lone Wolf".
和狼群在一起也挺有意思的
Sometimes it's fun to run with the pack.
这话说得对 保重 麦琪
You got a point. You take care, Maggy.
噢 我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
为了感谢你们 我的野蛮朋友
As a token of my gratitude, my violent friend,
我送你们一个回家的工具
I got you, and the little rascals a ride home.
瞧瞧
Behold!
什么
What?
就当是礼物吧
Consider it a gift.
老得都能进博物馆了
That thing belongs in a museum.
我们也是
We all do.
嗨 好玩吧
Hey. Fun, right?
对 很好玩
Yeah. Fun.
保重
Take care.
小心 小心 步步为营
Take care. Beware beware, what we care.
不要掉以轻心
Care for what you do.
老天没准会要你的命
Or mumbo jumbo's gonna hoodoo you.
Mumbo jumbo's gonna hoodoo you.
轰隆 轰隆 轰隆 轰
Boomalay boomalay boomalay boom!
敬比利
To Billy!
愿他安息
Rest in peace.
我要做个按摩
I need a massage.
别看着我
Don't look at me.
嗨
Hey.
干嘛
What?
有人托我捎句话
From one friend to another.
什么
What?
你得好好学学怎么打架
You really should learn how to fight.